要是被人看到怎么办？
What if someone sees?
没人看的
Nobody's going to see
天呐，不可理喻
Oh my God
好吧，快一点
Okay fine quickly
好
Okay
这会痒，这痒
That tickles, that tickles
你喜欢吗？
Do you like it?
喜欢
I do
停，等一下
Wait stop
我妈打来的
My mom's calling
所以呢？别管他就行了
So just ignore it
不行
No
别管了
Come on
不会有事的！
so what?
好吧，好吧
Okay Okay
莉莉，昨晚你跑哪了？
Lilly where were you last night?
哦，我在艾莉森家读书呢
Oh I was studying at Allison's house
我想她知道了
I think she knows
有人吗？
Hello?
谁在那儿？
Who's there?
妈妈？
Mom?
妈你在做什么？
Mom what are you doing?
她知道我们做了什么
She knows what we did
怎么会？我从街上接的你
How? I picked you up from down the street
我就该说去了图书馆的！！
I should have said the library
哪位？
Hello?
你好，艾莉森？我是莉莉的妈妈
Hello Allison? This is Lilly's mom
你要来点吗？
You want some?
没人会知道的
No one's going to know
行吧
Okay
大家好，这是你姨妈帕拉姆吉
Hello everybody it's your Auntie Paramjeet
你最好喜欢这部短片，不然我将呼你的脸
you better like this video or I am going to beat your face
下面评论，点赞，并订阅
Comment below give it thumbs up and do subscribing
最新视频在这，视频博客在那里
Last video over there, dumb vlog over there
你最好时常回来瞅瞅，我们正在
you better make sure you coming back because we
制作新视频
making new video okay
沙雕阿姨，在线拜拜
one love whatever God stupid go to room.